Guide to the African Collection, Yale University Library, Records of the Curator
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1965-1990; Accession 1998-A-127
  - Bloemfontein Provincial Library Service, 1970 June 1 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Bloomsbury Book Auctions, 1990 March (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Board of Trade and Industry, 1986 November 10 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Bode, Francis, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Bophuthtatswana University, 1988–1990 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Bordeaux Universite, 1975–1990 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Boston College, 1980–1992 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Boston Committee for the Liberation of Southern Africa, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Boston University, 1992 January–1994 December (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Boston University, 1983 January–1991 December (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Boston Univ. African Studies Center, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Botswana Society, 1970–1993 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Bowdoin College, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Bowling Green State University (Ohio), 1980–1982 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Bowman, Larry W. Professor, 1994–1997 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Boyd, Jean, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Mr. Joseph F. Boyle, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Bradford University, 1984 June 29 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Brandeis University, 1980–1981 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Universite de Brazzaville, Congo, 1975–1980 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Brenner, Louis, 1981–1985 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Brenthurst Library, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Bringham Young University, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Britain Zimbabew Society, 1994–1996 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - British Library (formerly British Museum), 1984–1986 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Brooklyn College Library, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Brown University, 1996–1997 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Bucknell University Press, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Mr. Robin Castell, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - City University of New York (CUNY), 1977–1986 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - California, University at Berkeley, 1978–1990 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - California, University at Irvine, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - California, University at Los Angeles, 1973–1993 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - California, University at Santa Cruz, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech), 1968 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Cape of Good Hope Foundation, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Cape Town University & University Library, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - University at Carbondale Southern Illinois, 1989–1996 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Casada, Jim Dr., 1992–1994 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Cassanelli, Lee Professor University of Pennsylvania, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences Stanford, CA, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Centre of African Studies, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - The Center for Research Libraries, 1989–1991 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - CRL Nigeria Since Independence Robison, David, director, 1973 November (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Central College-Pella, Iowa, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Centre Aequatoria, 1985–1998 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - The Center for Research Libraries, 1992–1996 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Chicago University Library, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, 1984–1985 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Choate School, Resource Center for Afro-American Studies Wallingford, Connecticut, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Mrs. Ilona R. Chukwudebe, 1988–1991 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - John Cinnamon, 1985–1991 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Circular Letters, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Civil Rights League (South Africa), 1967–1989 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Clark, Nancy (formerly Nancy Theis), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Clark, D.A., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Colenbrander, Dr. J.C.A.L., 1985–1991 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Colin Legum's (Third World Reports), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Collins, John, 1986–1989 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Colorado, University of, 1979–1990 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Columbia Univesity and Libraries III, 1978–1995 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Committee for Health in Southern Africa, 1987 December 15–1988 January 26 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - The Commonwealth Foundation, 1973 January 23 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Concerned Africanist Scholars, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Cone, L. Winston, 1982–1984 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Congo Film Production, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Connecticut College, 1973–1986 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - University of Connecticut, Storrs, 1972–1994 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Cork, University College, 1973 April 13 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Cornell University-Ithaca, New York, 1984–1992 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Council on Foreign Relations and Library, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Crawford & Balcarres, 1995 September 4 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Cuttington College, 1963–1970 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Cushingham, Stanley L., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Czechoslovak Academy, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Clarke, Walter, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Dakar University, 1963–1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Dakar University Institut Fondamental D'Afrique Noir, 1982–1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dalhousie University - Nova Scotia, 1977–1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Danilowitz, Brenda, 1991–1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dar es Salaam, University of, 1975–1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth College, 1983–1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Dauphin, Joanna - banking, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Davenport, Professor Rodney, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Geoffrey, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - University of Delaware, 1969–1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - University of Delhi, 1964–1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Denver University Center on International Race Relations, 1970–1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - DePauw University - Indiana, 1973 February 12 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Deutsche Afrika-Gesellschaft, 1967–1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Deutsches Institut fur Afrika-Furschung, 1967–1970 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Dhennequin, Michele, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Dick-Read, Robert, 1975–1982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Distributed Art Publishers, Incorporated, 1997 July 16 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Distribution/Fulfillment Department Films & Videos on/about Southern Africa, 1991 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Director of Association Suppliers, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Directory of Special Libraries and Information Centers, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Documentary Educational Resources, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Donnelley, Mr. Gaylord, 1989–1991 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Duke University Library - Durham, North Carolina, 1971–1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Duncan Stuart Publications, 1990 October 28 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Dunnington, Bruce, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Duquesne University Library, 1963–1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Durban Municipal Library, 1986–1989 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - University of Durban-Westville, 1973–1995 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Durham, England University, 1965–1988 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Earlham College, 1970–1981 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Earthscan, Undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Eastern African Centre for Research on Oral Traditions and African National Languages, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - The Economist Intelligence Unit, Undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Department of Education and Training, 1994 April 24 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Emeagwali, Gloria T., 1994 July–1994 August (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Emerald Isle Books, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - 1820 Settler's Association of South Africa - Johannesburg, South Africa, 1970 July–1970 September (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Elizabeth Seton College, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Emory University, 1984–1994 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Emory University - Pitts Theology Library, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Encyclopaedia of Sub-Saharan Africa, 1991–1993 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Episcopal Churchpeople for a Free Southern Africa, 1976–1997 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Equator Bank, Undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Erasmus Press, 1986 August (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Eskom Electricity Council, 1992 September (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Essex, University of, England, 1977–1983 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Essex Institute, Salem, Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Ethics & Public Policy Center, 1984 May–1984 October (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Etudes sur les Relations Islamo-Chretiennes, 1996 December (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Evalds, Victoria K., 1980 June 3 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Exeter University Library, 1976 December (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Farleigh Dickinson University, 1979–1981 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Fast Facts, 1991 October (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Felosaony Enterprises, 1996 October (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Fifth Pan-African Congress, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Financial Services Board, 1992 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Florida International University - Mr. Scott Kass, 1991 March (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Florida University, Gainesville, Florida, 1990–1998 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Focus on Africa magazine, 1991 July 25 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Fola Abbey Educational Book Services, 1990 October 9 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Ford Foundation, 1972–1977 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Fordham University, 1981–1995 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Foreign Book Services, 1995 January–1995 April (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Foundation for Education, Science, and Technology, 1994–1998 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Foundation for Global Dialogue, 1997 September 15 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Fulbright Association, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Furlong, Patrick Mr., 1993 May 9 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Furman University - Greenville, South Carolina, 1989 February 6 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Frankel, S. H., Undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Free Angola Information Service, 1991 February (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Free Market Foundation of Southern Africa, 1984 December 28 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - French West Africa, 1993 January 26 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Fund for Democratic Elections in South Africa, 1994 April (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Gale Research Company, 1988 November (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Galerie Amad African Arts, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Gamble, Professor David P., 1993–1998 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Genootskap Vir Afrikaanse Volkskunde, 1988–1992 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - George Mason University, 1998 January 8 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Georgetown University, 1980–1982 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - George Washington University, 1994–1998 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Georgia University Libraries, 1982–1989 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Gezira University, 1980 August 28 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Ghana Institute of Management and Public Administration, Greenhil, 1985 September 10 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Gleason, Judith, 1975–1990 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Government Documents Adviso, 1982 September 18 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Grahamstown Historical Society, 1993–1996 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Grahamstown Rural Committee, 1991–1992 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Great Epic Books, 1991–1993 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Group Interdiscinplinaire de Recherche sur l'Afrique, 1997 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Women Make Movies, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Greenwood Publishing Group, Incorporated, 1993 March (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Guelph University, 1987–1992 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Gunn, Ms. Alexia, 1994 February (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Gunn, Mrs. Virginia, 1993–1997 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Harare Working Group, 1988 June 28 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1981 June 29 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Hartford University, West Hartford, 1971–1983 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Harvard University Library, 1971–1995 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Harvard University Committee on African Studies, 1992–1993 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Harvard University, 1991–1992 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Harvard Negotiation Project, 1983 July 5 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Harvard University - Ms. Lois Fiore, Niemann Foundation, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Haverford College, 1986–1990 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Haydarabad Historical Society, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Health Education Network, 1990 October 4 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Heffers, 1990 May (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Heineman Educational Books, Limited, 1981 July 2 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Henderson, Professor Richard N., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1982–1987 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Hewssa Trust, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - The Highway Mail (Pty) Limited, 1993 July 8 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Heywood, Christopher, 1989 February 23 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Historical Firearms Society of South Africa, 1994 December 1 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - History Society of Zimbabwe, 1985–1991 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Historical Society of Nigeria, 1985 July 1 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Hlatshusayo, Dr. Simphiwe, 1993 November 3 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Highsmith Press, 1994 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Hobson, R., 1990–1996 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1982–1992 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - The Hobhouse Trust, 1994–1995 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Hofstra University, 1982 February 23 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Holleyman & Treacher, Limited, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Holmes & Meier Publishers, Incorporated, 1990–1994 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Holt, Wexler, & Merchant, 1990 June 28 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Hone, Mr. Basel T., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Hong Kong University, 1981 February 11 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Hoover Institution, 1990–1997 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Hoover Institution (Stanford), 1986–1992 (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - Hoover Institution Press, 1982 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Houston, University of, 1983–1997 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Houston Inter-University African Studies Program, 1970–1972 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Howard University, 1967–1995 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Hudson Institute, 1972–1977 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Hugo, Professor Pierre (UNISA), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Human Rights Commission, 1991–1994 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - Hunter Books, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Die Hugenote-Kollege, Wellington, South Africa, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Human Resources Network (Philadelphia), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Human Sciences Research Council, 1989–1991 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - The Hunger Project, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Hurd, Linwood, 1990–1993 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Ifo-Institut, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Instituto Nacional do Livro e do Disco (INLD), 1981–1982 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center, Incorporated (IRRC), 1991 February 27 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - ITT Boycott (Gulf Boycott Coalition), 1973–1977 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - ITT World Communications, Incorporated, 1988 January 31 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - Inter Documentation Company (IDC) Publishers, 1991–1996 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - IFAN (Dakar), 1987–1988 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Illinois University, 1994–1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Illorin University & Library (Nigeria), 1977–1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ilsley, Lucretial, 1975–1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Imperial War Museum, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Indian Council for Africa New Delhi, India, 1968–1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Indiana University, Bloomington, 1995–1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Indiana University African Studies Program, 1982–1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Indigo Publications, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Infodata Limited, U.S.A., 1989–1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Inkukuleko Publications, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Institut Africain pour le Development Economique et Social, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Institute Ethnology & African Studies, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Institut fur Afrika-Kunde, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Institut fur Auslandsbeziehungen Stuttgart, German (BRD), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Institut Islamique de Dakar, 1979 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Multi-Party Democracy, 1993 June 22 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Institut National pour les Sciences Humaines, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Institute for African Affairs (Tennessee State University), 1983 February 7 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Institute for African Alternatives, 1987–1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Industrial Education, Durban, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Institute of International Education, 1994–1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - The Institute for the Study of Man in Africa, Johannesburg, 1970–1990 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Institute of American Relations, 1981 July 21 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Institute of Black Research, 1981 September 1–1991 October 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1978–1995 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Defence Policy, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Institue of International Law & Economic Development-Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Personnel Management (SA), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Planning Research, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Social Studies-The Hague, 1981 October (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Institute of Town Clerks of Southern Africa, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Instituto Nacional de Estudos e Pesquisa, 1985–1989 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Inter Documentation Company, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - International African Institute II, 1976–1990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - International Centre for Bantu Civilisations, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - International Center for African Social and Economic Development, 1980 March 21 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - International Center for Development Policy, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - International Committee of the Red Cross, Geneva, 1969–1986 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - International Congress of Somali Studies, 1986 January 28 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - International Correspondence, 1982 January 8 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - International Council for Equality of Opportunity Principles Inc., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - International Center of Photography, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Irish Anti-Apartheid Movement, 1989–1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - International Defense & Aid Fund-Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1972–1990 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - International Development Research Centre, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - International Institute for Labor Studies, 1981 November (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - International Labour Research and Information Group, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - International League for Human Rights, 1981–1983 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - International Library of African Music, 1980–1986 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - International Peace Research Institute, Oslo, 1981–1982 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - International Studies Association, 1972–1978 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - International University Exchange Fund, 1975–1980 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - International Women's Tribune Centre, 1981 June 24 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center-Voorhees, Meg, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - The University of Iowa Libraries, 1990–1998 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Istituto Italiano Africa, 1969–1980 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Issue-based Indian Ocean Network, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Ivory Coast, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Dan Aiki Publications, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Lagos University & Library-Yaba, Lagos, 1967–1985 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - L'Harmattan, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Lamu Society Museum, 1975–1987 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Lamar University, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Ms. Elizabeth S. Landis, 1991 October (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Latrobe University, Australia, 1976–1992 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Mr. Premesh Lalu, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law, 1982–1994 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1986–1988 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Lee, Mrs. Janine, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Leeds University, 1965–1996 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Lehman College-City University of New York (CUNY), 1988 December 18 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Legal Resources Centre, 1985 June 18 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Dr. Lisbeth Levey, 1998 January 6 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Library of Congress-Washington, 1996 January–1998 March 17 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Library of Congress-Nairobi Office, 1991–1992 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Library Association, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Library of Congress-Nairobi, 1997 January–1997 December (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Leiden University, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Library of Congress-Washington, 1987–1997 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Library of Congress-Washington, 1993 January–1994 December (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Legum's Colin Third Wolrd Reports, 1994–1996 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Lems-Dworking, Carol Publishers, 1996 October (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Lentell, John, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Leonard, Richard, 1986–1987 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Michael Leslie, University of Florida School of Journalism, 1993 January 20 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Liberia National Archives, 1982–1989 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Liberia, University of, 1967–1987 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Librarians at United States Institutions with Major African Collections, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Library Company of Philadelphia, 1986 February 26 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - University of Libya, 1969–1980 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Loeb, Karl Mr., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - London University School of Oriental & African Studies (SOAS) II, 1976–1985 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - London University-German Historical Institute, 1985 March (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - London University Goldsmiths Library, 1981–1989 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - London School of Economics, 1960–1983 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Le Moyne College, 1985 November (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - London University School of Librarianship, Archives, & Information, 1984 February 17 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Longman Group Ltd., 1980–1984 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Louisiana State University, 1983–1992 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Luanda University, 1980 February (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Universite de Lubumbashi, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - London University Institute of Commonwealth Studies, 1963–1997 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Lloyds Bank, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Magic, 1980–1981 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Mahomed S. Bhana's Agency, 1994–1995 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - University of Maiduguri, 1990–1991 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Makerere University, 1996 June 12 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Malik, Abdul Processing, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - McGill University, 1982–1986 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - McGill University Centre for Developing-Area Studies, 1971–1992 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Mail Publications Group, 1990 July 9 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Maine University, 1982 October 13 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Mainz University, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - Malatsi, Mosebjane, 1994 August 12 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Makerere Institute of Social Research (MISR), 1971–1975 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Manchester University & John Rylands Univ. Lib. Of Manchester, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - The Manica Trading Company, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Maryland University Journal of Southern African Affairs, 1974–1988 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - Maskew Miller Longman, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Boston, Massachusetts, 1969–1990 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Mr. Andrew Manley, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Marquette University, 1994 October 12 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Mass. University, 1967–1988 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - University of Mauritius-Reduit, 1971–1993 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Henry & Olga May, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Mazenod Institute, 1971 December 8 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Mrs. Michael T. McRae, 1990 June 29 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - University of Melbourne Library, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mellen, Education Company (Lewiston, New York), 1995 August 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mellon Foundation, 1996 May 6 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Memphis State University, 1975–1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mercy College, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)